<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Software Engineering on Blog | Dwarkanath Prabhu</title>
    <link>/tags/software-engineering/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Software Engineering on Blog | Dwarkanath Prabhu</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 22:39:33 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/tags/software-engineering/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How I Use AI</title>
      <link>/posts/how-i-use-ai/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 22:39:33 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/how-i-use-ai/</guid>
      <description>Unless you live under a rock you must have heard of Artificial Intelligence (AI). It is an umbrella term for any computer program that can perform human-like intelligent tasks (eg. identifying animals) but has come to be interchangeable with Generative AI like ChatGPT.&#xA;Generative AI is, as the name suggests, any tool that &amp;ldquo;generates&amp;rdquo; output like a human would. It could be an essay, an image or code. ChatGPT was not the first Generative AI app but it&amp;rsquo;s selling point was so dead simple it became the most popular very quickly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Software Engineering Interview Preparation</title>
      <link>/posts/software-engineering-interview-preparation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 23:16:01 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/software-engineering-interview-preparation/</guid>
      <description>While looking for software engineering jobs, I&amp;rsquo;ve gone through a lot of preparation material. Typically, technical interviews will take 3 forms -&#xA;Data Structures and Algorithms System Design Low-level Design / Object-oriented Design The links above have all my notes compiled in one place for each topic. I&amp;rsquo;m using Notion to write these notes.&#xA;A few disclaimers:&#xA;This is not complete and I will keep adding to these as I study more I have added sources wherever possible for readers to read more from Since this is manually written there are bound to be errors.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
